{
    "id": "c418e4e73a8d40a1a0b78bc89b9a4e8e",
    "title": "If or unless grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "393ce39d97a9401d9202c59e3a59358e",
            "title": "If And Unless Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………. you eat too much, you will fall ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. he doesn’t mend his ways, he will lose his job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………… you don’t stop smoking, you will fall seriously ill.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I wouldn’t have won ……………….. he hadn’t helped me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… he mends his ways, he will land in serious trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will take the job ………………… the pay is too low.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be back tomorrow ………………… there is a train strike.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will quit my job ……………….. they don’t offer me a raise.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will be surprised …………………. she doesn’t recognize me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You will look prettier ……………….. you don’t wear so much make-up.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}